[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1, "question": "Who's got the real answer to fixing the economy?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "got", "the", "real", "answer", "to", "fixing", "the", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 2, "answer": "President Obama has decided to attack success.", "answer_tokens": ["President", "Obama", "has", "decided", "to", "attack", "success", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Great, it's great to be here.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", ",", "it", "'s", "great", "to", "be", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Has he always done the right thing for those companies?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "always", "done", "the", "right", "thing", "for", "those", "companies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Maybe not, maybe 20 percent that they say haven't worked out.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "not", ",", "maybe", "20", "percent", "that", "they", "say", "have", "n't", "worked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "When am I not honest?", "question_tokens": ["When", "am", "I", "not", "honest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I'm disputing for a moment your integrity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "disputing", "for", "a", "moment", "your", "integrity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "-- it was about job creation?", "question_tokens": ["--", "it", "was", "about", "job", "creation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I think making the job creation argument was not the smartest case to make.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "making", "the", "job", "creation", "argument", "was", "not", "the", "smartest", "case", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you think this will be the key battleground, the ideological dispute we're now seeing over this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "this", "will", "be", "the", "key", "battleground", ",", "the", "ideological", "dispute", "we", "'re", "now", "seeing", "over", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "If it is, Romney ought to wipe it out.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "it", "is", ",", "Romney", "ought", "to", "wipe", "it", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"], "PERSON": ["Howard Schultz"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "No, but does it keep jobs, Piers, yes?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "does", "it", "keep", "jobs", ",", "Piers", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "This -- plays something from an interview I did with Howard Schultz from Starbucks on this show.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "--", "plays", "something", "from", "an", "interview", "I", "did", "with", "Howard", "Schultz", "from", "Starbucks", "on", "this", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What is your opinion of the whole IPO launch of Facebook this week?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "opinion", "of", "the", "whole", "IPO", "launch", "of", "Facebook", "this", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Ugly.", "answer_tokens": ["Ugly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "How after everything that we've been through in the last few years, could a company make that kind of loss without apparently some of the top people having any idea?", "question_tokens": ["How", "after", "everything", "that", "we", "'ve", "been", "through", "in", "the", "last", "few", "years", ",", "could", "a", "company", "make", "that", "kind", "of", "loss", "without", "apparently", "some", "of", "the", "top", "people", "having", "any", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Some people made a mistake.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "people", "made", "a", "mistake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last few years"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "TO", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "How Jamie Dimon dealt with this properly?", "question_tokens": ["How", "Jamie", "Dimon", "dealt", "with", "this", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Right up to now, absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "up", "to", "now", ",", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jamie Dimon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "So if you're -- if you're an average American watching this and they're saying, how can a company lose over $2 billion, maybe $3 billion?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "you", "'re", "--", "if", "you", "'re", "an", "average", "American", "watching", "this", "and", "they", "'re", "saying", ",", "how", "can", "a", "company", "lose", "over", "$", "2", "billion", ",", "maybe", "$", "3", "billion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "RB", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Of its own money.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "its", "own", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$2 billion", "$3 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Do you suspect that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "suspect", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No, we don't suspect that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "suspect", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "What do you suspect was going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "suspect", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "They were trying to hedge the (INAUDIBLE) slid into something else.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "trying", "to", "hedge", "the", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "slid", "into", "something", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Is he right to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["2.5 percent"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Should people be feeling generally more confident?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "people", "be", "feeling", "generally", "more", "confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Pretty good, it's not great, it's nowhere near what we need and we're going to grow in the 2 to 2.5 percent range over the next couple of quarters.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "good", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "great", ",", "it", "'s", "nowhere", "near", "what", "we", "need", "and", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "grow", "in", "the", "2", "to", "2.5", "percent", "range", "over", "the", "next", "couple", "of", "quarters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "But a lot better than it was, say, three years ago?", "question_tokens": ["But", "a", "lot", "better", "than", "it", "was", ",", "say", ",", "three", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VB", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "A lot better than it was three years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "better", "than", "it", "was", "three", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "So Obama has done a pretty good job then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "Obama", "has", "done", "a", "pretty", "good", "job", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, he's done a job of bringing it back in the cycle.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "done", "a", "job", "of", "bringing", "it", "back", "in", "the", "cycle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Do you give him due credit for that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "give", "him", "due", "credit", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "No, I don't like what he's done.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "like", "what", "he", "'s", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "What do you give him credit for in terms of the economy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "give", "him", "credit", "for", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "That's a tough one for me.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "tough", "one", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I was very fortunate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "very", "fortunate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1996"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "When was the last time you actually spoke, you two?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "actually", "spoke", ",", "you", "two", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "That was 1996.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "1996", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Can you repeat them?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "repeat", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "No, no, it wasn't like that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Who said that, \"I'm done\"?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "said", "that", ",", "``", "I", "'m", "done", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What is the single biggest offer you have had to put it all behind you and get back on a stage together?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "single", "biggest", "offer", "you", "have", "had", "to", "put", "it", "all", "behind", "you", "and", "get", "back", "on", "a", "stage", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, I've heard a lot of numbers --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "heard", "a", "lot", "of", "numbers", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Seven figures, eight figures?", "question_tokens": ["Seven", "figures", ",", "eight", "figures", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I'd say, I'd say it starts off with seven figures, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", ",", "I", "'d", "say", "it", "starts", "off", "with", "seven", "figures", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Is there any check that would tempt you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "check", "that", "would", "tempt", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I don't think it's a matter of that, it really isn't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "matter", "of", "that", ",", "it", "really", "is", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "And so I don't think there's a price tag that anybody's going to put in front of us that's going to make that work, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "price", "tag", "that", "anybody", "'s", "going", "to", "put", "in", "front", "of", "us", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "make", "that", "work", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Let's take a short break.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "take", "a", "short", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Argentina"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 380, "question": "What was the moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, you're talking about a concert that was in -- I think it was in Argentina, back in the '90s, I mentioned in the interview we did before, which was when it was pouring really thick rain and there was steam coming off the audience and we were playing \"November Rain\" and the timing was such that as soon as we went into the cords of \"November Rain\" this rainstorm started and just seeing this crowd sort of bouncing in the rhythm of the song and the --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "a", "concert", "that", "was", "in", "--", "I", "think", "it", "was", "in", "Argentina", ",", "back", "in", "the", "'90s", ",", "I", "mentioned", "in", "the", "interview", "we", "did", "before", ",", "which", "was", "when", "it", "was", "pouring", "really", "thick", "rain", "and", "there", "was", "steam", "coming", "off", "the", "audience", "and", "we", "were", "playing", "``", "November", "Rain", "''", "and", "the", "timing", "was", "such", "that", "as", "soon", "as", "we", "went", "into", "the", "cords", "of", "``", "November", "Rain", "''", "this", "rainstorm", "started", "and", "just", "seeing", "this", "crowd", "sort", "of", "bouncing", "in", "the", "rhythm", "of", "the", "song", "and", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "And for someone like me who's never going to come close to that, what is the -- what is the physical experience?", "question_tokens": ["And", "for", "someone", "like", "me", "who", "'s", "never", "going", "to", "come", "close", "to", "that", ",", "what", "is", "the", "--", "what", "is", "the", "physical", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "The physical experience is there's the energy of the band playing a very heartfelt song, you know, and then you have that interaction with an audience that's reacting to that and it's a huge amount of energy.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "physical", "experience", "is", "there", "'s", "the", "energy", "of", "the", "band", "playing", "a", "very", "heartfelt", "song", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "then", "you", "have", "that", "interaction", "with", "an", "audience", "that", "'s", "reacting", "to", "that", "and", "it", "'s", "a", "huge", "amount", "of", "energy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Do you feel remotely English?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "remotely", "English", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes, I feel very connected to my British roots.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "feel", "very", "connected", "to", "my", "British", "roots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iggy Pop"], "LOCATION": ["OK"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "If you were creating a super group, all the talent that you have ever seen, played with, whatever, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "creating", "a", "super", "group", ",", "all", "the", "talent", "that", "you", "have", "ever", "seen", ",", "played", "with", ",", "whatever", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, I mean, some of those people -- well, OK, if you're about people that are living that I've actually played with before, Iggy Pop is great.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "some", "of", "those", "people", "--", "well", ",", "OK", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "about", "people", "that", "are", "living", "that", "I", "'ve", "actually", "played", "with", "before", ",", "Iggy", "Pop", "is", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Who would be your drummer?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "your", "drummer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "That's what I'm trying to figure out.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "trying", "to", "figure", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack White"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "No one wants to do this, but who would play the other guitarist to you?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "wants", "to", "do", "this", ",", "but", "who", "would", "play", "the", "other", "guitarist", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "It would be cool to jam with Jack White.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "cool", "to", "jam", "with", "Jack", "White", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What did you think of what he said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I mean, that was really sweet, but he's a really great guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "was", "really", "sweet", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "a", "really", "great", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Slash, you, basically, you're a rock star and I have discussed it with you before, but for the benefit of this interview, I just want to -- you've been clean, what, six years now?", "question_tokens": ["Slash", ",", "you", ",", "basically", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "rock", "star", "and", "I", "have", "discussed", "it", "with", "you", "before", ",", "but", "for", "the", "benefit", "of", "this", "interview", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "--", "you", "'ve", "been", "clean", ",", "what", ",", "six", "years", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Almost seven.", "answer_tokens": ["Almost", "seven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What was the thing that got you out of it, personally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "thing", "that", "got", "you", "out", "of", "it", ",", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Being able to look at it from both sides, not being so out of it that I couldn't get some sort of a perspective on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "able", "to", "look", "at", "it", "from", "both", "sides", ",", "not", "being", "so", "out", "of", "it", "that", "I", "could", "n't", "get", "some", "sort", "of", "a", "perspective", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "You chose to end up hiring a number of hotel rooms in the same hotel, for various women, none of who knew about each other?", "question_tokens": ["You", "chose", "to", "end", "up", "hiring", "a", "number", "of", "hotel", "rooms", "in", "the", "same", "hotel", ",", "for", "various", "women", ",", "none", "of", "who", "knew", "about", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Expensive, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Expensive", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "It was a little bit expensive.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "little", "bit", "expensive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Do you feel like you have met your match with her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "have", "met", "your", "match", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Yeah, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Is that what you needed to do?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "needed", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "When she and I first met, I knew that I was hooked when we first met and I tried to keep my distance from her for a long time because I knew once that relationship was seriously established, things were going to change.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "she", "and", "I", "first", "met", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "I", "was", "hooked", "when", "we", "first", "met", "and", "I", "tried", "to", "keep", "my", "distance", "from", "her", "for", "a", "long", "time", "because", "I", "knew", "once", "that", "relationship", "was", "seriously", "established", ",", "things", "were", "going", "to", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How many timings would you say in your life you have been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "timings", "would", "you", "say", "in", "your", "life", "you", "have", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I would say properly, that was the first time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "properly", ",", "that", "was", "the", "first", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "ORGAN: Are you good dad?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Are", "you", "good", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I really try.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Do you have one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I don't have like an unachieved dream.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "like", "an", "unachieved", "dream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Was it for you a great honor to be inducted into the hall of fame?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "for", "you", "a", "great", "honor", "to", "be", "inducted", "into", "the", "hall", "of", "fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Yes, of course, it was a great honor.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", ",", "it", "was", "a", "great", "honor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Did you understand where Axl was coming from with his protests about it all?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "understand", "where", "Axl", "was", "coming", "from", "with", "his", "protests", "about", "it", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I didn't even really read it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "even", "really", "read", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Axl"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "You think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "A template for your life.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "template", "for", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Oh, Muslim?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "Muslim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Muslim.", "answer_tokens": ["Muslim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "You've written 77 books?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "written", "77", "books", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Well, I and some of my editors have worked on a lot of these books, too, but they're very, very good books.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "and", "some", "of", "my", "editors", "have", "worked", "on", "a", "lot", "of", "these", "books", ",", "too", ",", "but", "they", "'re", "very", ",", "very", "good", "books", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Are you related to him?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "related", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, who knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "who", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Isn't that the point of America, that none of you are?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "the", "point", "of", "America", ",", "that", "none", "of", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "We are all American.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "all", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 562, "question": "What's the last thing you would want to eat?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "last", "thing", "you", "would", "want", "to", "eat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "If I were thinking about food at that point ...", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "were", "thinking", "about", "food", "at", "that", "point", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "If I was very hungry and I was told that I only had an hour?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "very", "hungry", "and", "I", "was", "told", "that", "I", "only", "had", "an", "hour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What would you start with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Probably good, fresh eggs.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "good", ",", "fresh", "eggs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "And the main course, what would you have?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "main", "course", ",", "what", "would", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "That's my main course.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "my", "main", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Well, again, where do you think that came from, fish and chips?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "where", "do", "you", "think", "that", "came", "from", ",", "fish", "and", "chips", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Britain.", "answer_tokens": ["Britain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Where are the mushy peas?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "the", "mushy", "peas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, they're somewhere in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "somewhere", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Do you like mushy peas?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "mushy", "peas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Yes, they're okay.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "'re", "okay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Right out of the can, right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "out", "of", "the", "can", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "But you would seriously just have eggs as your last meal?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "would", "seriously", "just", "have", "eggs", "as", "your", "last", "meal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 614, "question": "American or French?", "question_tokens": ["American", "or", "French", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Or maybe a couple of bottles, if I knew I was going ...", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "maybe", "a", "couple", "of", "bottles", ",", "if", "I", "knew", "I", "was", "going", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "You wouldn't have American wine, would you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "have", "American", "wine", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "It depends.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "ORGAN: Wouldn't you go for a nice burgundy?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Would", "n't", "you", "go", "for", "a", "nice", "burgundy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I love white burgundy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "white", "burgundy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Of all these dishes in here, which are the ones that you were most excited, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "these", "dishes", "in", "here", ",", "which", "are", "the", "ones", "that", "you", "were", "most", "excited", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "The pies.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "pies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Why pies?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "pies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "I think pies are so typically American.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "pies", "are", "so", "typically", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Pardon?", "question_tokens": ["Pardon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Cobblers.", "answer_tokens": ["Cobblers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Cobblers are for shoes?", "question_tokens": ["Cobblers", "are", "for", "shoes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "It can be or they can be a derogatory term.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "can", "be", "or", "they", "can", "be", "a", "derogatory", "term", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "Yes, I will.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Apple, cherry, plum, what do you like?", "question_tokens": ["Apple", ",", "cherry", ",", "plum", ",", "what", "do", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I love lemon meringue.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "lemon", "meringue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "You still enjoy cooking?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "enjoy", "cooking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "What's the Martha Wrap?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "Martha", "Wrap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Something I sort of created.", "answer_tokens": ["Something", "I", "sort", "of", "created", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Can I plug it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "plug", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Tell me what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Are you a big griller?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "big", "griller", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "I'm a careful griller.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "careful", "griller", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "What's the secret to a good barbecue?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", "to", "a", "good", "barbecue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Well, there's a lot of secrets.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "secrets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What bit of advice would you give me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "bit", "of", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "OK, a hot, hot fire.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "a", "hot", ",", "hot", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Burned?", "question_tokens": ["Burned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Not like completely black coated, but a little dash of black.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "like", "completely", "black", "coated", ",", "but", "a", "little", "dash", "of", "black", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you press your hamburgers on the grill?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "press", "your", "hamburgers", "on", "the", "grill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "You compact them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "compact", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes, I like them all sort of compacted and blackened.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "like", "them", "all", "sort", "of", "compacted", "and", "blackened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]